[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress portrayed Sams girlfriend, Mikaela Banes, in the 2009 science fiction movie Transformers: Revenge of the Fallen?", "correct_answer": "Megan Fox", "incorrect_answers": ["Angelina Jolie", "Jennifer Aniston", "Lindsay Lohan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A computer that has wireless 802.11b/g or a Nic card needs nothing else to connect to the Internet.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From 1984-1992 John Larroquette portrayed the Assistant District Attorny on Night Court. What was the name of his character?", "correct_answer": "Dan Fielding", "incorrect_answers": ["Mac Robinson", "Harry Stone", "Chris  Sullivan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to an urban legend, in Geneva in 2002 an intoxicated groom was suffocated at his bachelor party by which of the following?", "correct_answer": "A strippers large breasts", "incorrect_answers": ["Passing out face down on the shag carpet", "His jealous best man", "His own tie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the first 3-D film?", "correct_answer": "The Power of Love", "incorrect_answers": ["The Strange Boy", "The Power of the Thing", "It Flew to Earth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This technique is used to relax soft tissue. It is done using both hands, exercising light pressure.", "correct_answer": "Effleurage", "incorrect_answers": ["Tapotement", "Friction", "Petrissage"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the Smallville series, Superman has the strength of how many men?", "correct_answer": "10 men", "incorrect_answers": ["1,000 men", "100,000,000", "100 men"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which state was the first to ratify the Constitution of the United States in 1787?", "correct_answer": "Delaware", "incorrect_answers": ["Massachusetts", "Rhode Island", "Pennsylvania"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The mango fruit is the national fruit of this country.", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["The Philippines", "Pakistan", "India"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these is an operating system?", "correct_answer": "Vista", "incorrect_answers": ["Norton Anti-Virus", "Office -  Professional edition", "Microsoft"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many calories does whole milk contain per serving of 8 fluid ounces?", "correct_answer": "150", "incorrect_answers": ["102", "98", "180"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ren\u00e9 Th\u00e9ophile Hyacinthe La\u00ebnnec (1781-1826) invented this important item, still in use today.", "correct_answer": "The stethoscope", "incorrect_answers": ["The dental drill", "The safety pin", "The chalkboard"]}]